malaysiantoday.com.my 2004-12-07

# Malaysian Today Web Edition - Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement for Malaysian Today Web Edition 

The Malaysian Today Press Sdn. Bhd. (co. no. 518445-A) has created this privacy statement to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, Malaysian Today Web Edition. 

**Information collected by Malaysian Today Web Edition**

Our Web servers do not automatically recognise specific information about individual users on our site. In addition, our servers do not automatically record information regarding a user's e-mail address unless the user supplies it. 

We use cookies so that you don't have to re-enter your login information each time you visit our site. 

We collect information about users during the registration process for certain parts of our site; through their participation in certain activities, including contests, forums, and polls; and through the use of cookies. When you request pages from our server, it automatically collects some information about your preferences, including your IP address. We use this to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our site. 

The information collected is meant to identify the broad demographic profile of our users. This information does not contain anything that can identify users individually. We may combine demographic information supplied by a subscriber at registration with site usage data to provide profiles, in aggregate form, about our users and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. You may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products or services in our newspaper or on our site. 

The user-supplied information collected through the registration process, surveys, contest entry forms, polls or other similar vehicles is used to improve the content of our site, or used for The Malaysian Today Press Sdn. Bhd.’s marketing purposes. It is not shared with other organisations for commercial purposes unless specifically stated. We may use such information for targeting appropriate editorial or advertising content to users but users will always be able to opt out of such mailings. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, and/or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We respect freedom of speech and request that users respect one another in exercising said freedom. 

**General**

This site contains links to other sites. Malaysian Today Web Edition is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Malaysian Today Web Edition has also established relationships with partners but such relationships are generally technical in nature, or content collaborations. If any partner has access to any information entered by users in our database, this fact shall be disclosed to the user upon initiating the registration process. Users who feel they do not wish their information to be shared by anyone other than Malaysian Today Web Edition may then opt out of completing the registration. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When a user is asked to provide his/her credit card information, we provide a secure environment through our partners' systems (using industry standard SSL or SET protocols) for this purpose. 

**Contacting Malaysian Today Web Edition**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you may contact: 

The Malaysian Today Press Sdn. Bhd.  
Lot 3293 Section 64, Jalan Kwong Lee Bank  
93450 Kuching, Sarawak, Malaysia  
Email.: [tmtoday@tm.net.my](mailto:tmtoday@tm.net.my)

** To read our full stories, subscribe to the printed edition by calling us at 082-488181.**
